{
    "title": "COS102Exam",
    "time_limit_minutes": 7,
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "2 + 2",
            "options": [
                "3",
                "84",
                "4",
                "1"
            ],
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "X = 2, what is x",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "Not sure",
                "2",
                "x"
            ],
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "1m = ?cm",
            "options": [
                "10",
                "1000",
                "10000000",
                "100"
            ],
            "answer": "10000000"
        },
        {
            "question": "What continent are we in",
            "options": [
                "Africa",
                "Nigeria",
                "Lagos",
                "Earth"
            ],
            "answer": "Africa"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many fingers do we have",
            "options": [
                "11",
                "5",
                "7",
                "10"
            ],
            "answer": "10"
        },
        {
            "question": "what letter is missing _ump",
            "options": [
                "z",
                "J",
                "x",
                "c"
            ],
            "answer": "J"
        },
        {
            "question": "Pythons logo is a ?",
            "options": [
                "snake",
                "monkey",
                "crab",
                "dog"
            ],
            "answer": "snake"
        },
        {
            "question": "2 + 4",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "34",
                "12",
                "6"
            ],
            "answer": "6"
        },
        {
            "question": "1 * 0",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "0",
                "3",
                "6"
            ],
            "answer": "0"
        },
        {
            "question": "well p kd",
            "options": [
                "coolo",
                "adjk",
                "akldjfd",
                "dkfjkd"
            ],
            "answer": "akldjfd"
        }
    ]
}